MYLLA CHIZU SASAKI

GAME PROGRAMMER | UNITY3D DEVELOPER



O Curitiba, PR - Brazil



in /mylla-sasaki-b18268123



/mysasaki

ABOUT

Focused and enthusiastic graduate who aims to enhance developing skills, learn new experiences and join the game industry.

Has 7-month professional experience in Unity3D, including VR development.

Portfolio also includes multiplayer games developed while in college.

DEVELOPMENT SKILLS

Unity3D	SCRUM
Swift	SQL
Java	C++

LANGUAGES

ADDITIONAL

Good teamwork and communication.

Active participation in game jams.

Intermediate knowledge in programming patterns.

Professional experience in multiplayer development.

Professional experience in Unity VR development.

EDUCATION

2016 - 2019

DEGREE IN GAME DEVELOPMENT

PONTIFÍCIA UNIVERSIDADE CATÓLICA DO PARANÁ

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

March, 2019 - October, 2019

ZOYD SOFTWARES

INTERN UNITY DEVELOPER

Developed games, mobile and VR applications using Unity3D.

Wrote, modified and debugged C# scripts.

Reviewed and solved optimization issues.

Reported projects progress daily.

OTHER EXPERIENCES

2016 - 2017

SCIENTIFIC RESEARCH

SCHOLARSHIP STUDENT AS RESEARCHER

Researched about Game Jams and Hackathons and their benefits.

Developed an application to be used in these events.

2017 - 2018

APPLE DEVELOPER ACADEMY

SCHOLARSHIP STUDENT AS PROGRAMMER

Studied and developed iOS applications and games using Challenge Based Learning methodology. Worked with many teams in order to develop team work and healthy work environment.

CONTACT



+55 41 99270-2661



sasakimylla@gmail.com